<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>金融词条</title>
    <link>https://jinrongcitiao.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on 金融词条</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>金融词条</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 02:13:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jinrongcitiao.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://jinrongcitiao.github.io/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jinrongcitiao.github.io/page/about/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>基本面分析</title>
      <link>https://jinrongcitiao.github.io/articles/fundamental-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jinrongcitiao.github.io/articles/fundamental-analysis/</guid>
      <description>什么是基本面分析 基本面分析是对经济影响,行业变化,及公司的潜在力量的考察. 与大多数分析一样, 其目标是从未来价格走势中得出预测并从中获利.
Fundamental analysis is the examination of the underlying forces that affect the well being of the economy, industry groups, and companies. As with most analysis, the goal is to derive a forecast and profit from future price movements. At the company level, fundamental analysis may involve examination of financial data, management, business concept and competition. At the industry level, there might be an examination of supply and demand forces for the products offered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://jinrongcitiao.github.io/page/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2015 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jinrongcitiao.github.io/page/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact Aenean ipsum justo, semper eu nisl ut, pretium tincidunt sem. Praesent et diam sit amet lacus lobortis dictum a id lacus. Quisque hendrerit sit amet turpis eu varius. Ut id lorem ac felis ultrices tincidunt. Pellentesque consequat arcu ac fringilla imperdiet. Phasellus pellentesque, sapien non pulvinar blandit, sapien ante aliquet felis, vel porttitor sapien ante in lacus. Fusce non urna aliquet, malesuada nibh vel, luctus urna. Phasellus ut lacus molestie, varius purus quis, malesuada lorem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My awesome project</title>
      <link>https://jinrongcitiao.github.io/project/my-awesome-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2014 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jinrongcitiao.github.io/project/my-awesome-project/</guid>
      <description>About project Aenean ipsum justo, semper eu nisl ut, pretium tincidunt sem. Praesent et diam sit amet lacus lobortis dictum a id lacus. Quisque hendrerit sit amet turpis eu varius. Ut id lorem ac felis ultrices tincidunt. Pellentesque consequat arcu ac fringilla imperdiet. Phasellus pellentesque, sapien non pulvinar blandit, sapien ante aliquet felis, vel porttitor sapien ante in lacus. Fusce non urna aliquet, malesuada nibh vel, luctus urna. Phasellus ut lacus molestie, varius purus quis, malesuada lorem.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
